Finding Aid for Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project Records 1993-2008
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project Records 1993-2008
Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project.
16.5 linear feet
Organization founded in 1995 to encourage increased visibility and acceptance and appreciation of the lesbian/gay/bisexual and transgender community in Washtenaw County through education and political action. Materials received by the Bentley Historical Library in 2001 contain records primarily from the 1990s while materials received in 2013 are made up of records mostly from the 2000s. This organization's records contain meeting minutes, staff communications through email, and other documents relevant to the operation of the organization as well as how they carried out events and projects that aided the organization's purpose.
0268 Bj 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The record group was donated by the Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project (donor no. 9143 ) and came to the library in two accessions: September 2001 and July 2013.
The collection is open for research.
Founded in 1995, the Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project (WRAP) was an outgrowth of an earlier organization, the Ann Arbor/Washtenaw County chapter of the Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity. The statewide organization of the Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity was established to enlist opposition to a state ballot initiative that would deny equal discrimination protection to gay men and lesbians. After the initiative failed, members of the Washtenaw MCHD then decided to focus their attention on grassroot work within Washtenaw County, devoting themselves to increased visibility and acceptance and appreciation of the lesbian/gay/bisexual and transgender community through education and political action. To this end, they formed a new political action group, the Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project.
In 1997 WRAP received a $15,000 grant from the HOPE Foundation. From this period onward, the organization was able to expand their involvement in such political action efforts as National Coming Out Day, and such educational endeavors as the Gay, Lesbian, Straight Education Network (GLSEN).
In 2000 WRAP began participating in a project of note in Ann Arbor and Washtenaw County to encourage the growth of scouting for Equality (sfE) as an alternative to the Boys Scouts of America after they created a discriminatory policy excluding gay members. They also have continued to host a number of important and re-occurring events that for the benefit of members of their organization and the gay community in addition to serving as a resource center for LGBTQA groups and residents of Washtenaw County.
In December 2010, Washtenaw Rainbow Action Center changed the organization's name to the Jim Toy Community Center. Jim Toy was one of the first people to come out publicly in the state of Michigan and is a leader of gay rights activism in Michigan. He was also a founding member of WRAP and served on the Board of Directors.
The Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project records came to the library in two accessions, in September 2001 and July 2013. The 2001 accession material (3.5 linear feet, Boxes 1-4) includes the earliest records in the WRAP record group and date from the period when the Ann Arbor/Washtenaw County chapter of the Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity was active in its opposition to the 1994 anti-gay ballot proposal. The bulk of the records in this accession, however, date from the period of 1995 to 2000 following the reorganization of MCHD-Washtenaw into the Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project. They reflect well the day-to-day workings of the organization, its publicity efforts and the various events it sponsored.
The 2001 accession material (3.5 linear feet) is divided into four series: Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity - Washtenaw County chapter, 1993-1995; Administrative; Education and Outreach; and Political Action. Much of the communication done within the organization was handled through e-mail. This included correspondence and minutes of board meetings. As a result, casual and tangential matters often became part of the official record. To conserve space while preserving the integrity of a train of thought or "conversation," the processing archivists decided to retain the final copy of a message as it usually also contained a long string of previous forwards and replies. Much of the material in the record group, particularly meeting minutes and correspondence, was recorded by Jim Toy, an active member of WRAP's board of directors and onetime secretary.
The 2013 accession material (16 linear feet, Boxes 5-17) contains mostly documents from the early 2000s. Material in the 2013 accession is divided into four series: Administrative, Events, Finance, and Projects. A large portion of the WRAP records in this accession are staff communications through email, particularly in the Administrative, and Events and Projects, series.
Subjects:
Boy Scouts of America.; Gay, Lesbian, and Straight Education Network.; Human Rights Campaign (U.S.); Jim Toy Community Center.; Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity. Washtenaw County chapter.; Rainbow Oasis Center.; United Way of America.; Washtenaw Rainbow Action Project.; Coming out (Sexual orientation)--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Gay rights--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Gays--Legal status, laws, etc.--Michigan--Washtenaw County.
- Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity-Washtenaw County chapter 1993-1995
  The Michigan Campaign for Human Dignity - Washtenaw County chapter series consists of materials relating to the ballot campaign of 1994 and to the name change and reorganization MCHD into the Washtenaw Rainbow Action Program.
  - Ballot Campaign 1994 (Box 1)
  - Informational materials 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Name change and reorganization 1994-1995 (Box 1)
  - Statement of incorporation 1993 (Box 1)
  - Washtenaw Steering Committee, agendas and minutes 1993-1994 (Box 1)
  - Washtenaw United Way 1994 (Box 1)
    (funding of organizations opposed to equal rights for G/L)
- Administrative
  The Administrative series includes correspondence between board members, meeting minutes and agendas, budget information, and other work performed by WRAP's leaders. Prevalent in the Administrative series are working files made up of agendas, minutes, and notes from meetings of the Board of Directors, as well as those of WRAP's various committees. The working files include all types of documents that contributed to the day-to-day running of this organization, ranging from an Executive Director evaluation to event flyers and staff emails. The Administrative series also includes many records from the Board of Directors, various committees, and forms used to conduct and facilitate work in the office and resource center. Researchers will find material received with the 2001 accession in Boxes 1-2; material received with the 2013 accession in Boxes 5-13.
  - Addresses 1996-1999 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Board of Directors
    - Minutes and Agendas 1995-October 2000, 6 folders (Box 1)
    - Board of directors and advisory committee members (Box 1)
  - Budgets and financial reports 1998-2000 (Box 1)
  - Bylaws
    - 1995-1997 (Box 1)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 1)
  - Clippings 1998 (Box 1)
  - Commitment statements 1997 (Box 1)
  - Donor prospects 1995 (Box 1)
  - E-mail and notes
    - February 1995-September 1997 (Box 1)
    - September 1997-December 1997 (Box 1)
    - January 1998-August 1998 (Box 1)
    - September 1998-December 1998 (Box 1)
    - January 1999-March 1999 (Box 1)
    - April 1999-December 1999 (Box 1)
    - June 2000-October 2000 (Box 1)
  - LGBT Planned Community questionnaire 1999 (Box 1)
  - Mission and objectives 1995-1997 (Box 1)
  - Nomination Committee 1997 (Box 1)
  - Public Policy Committee -- Meeting minutes, agendas, correspondence regarding needs assessment, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Public Relations 1995-1997 (Box 2)
  - Public Relations information manual, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Relations with "Affirmations," September 1997 (Box 2)
  - Renting space from /aut/ Bar (Box 2)
  - Retirement Center Task Force -- Agendas, correspondence 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - Retirement Center Task Force -- Surveys 1999 (Box 2)
  - Sheats, Kenn (complaints against and removal from the advisory committee) (Box 2)
  - Strategic planning retreat 1999 (Box 2)
  - Website -- Robert Trombley August 2000-September 2000 (Box 2)
  - WRAP-authored articles 1997 (Box 2)
  - Academic Service Learning: client proposal and WRAP flyer (Box 5)
  - Affirmations Lesbian, Gay Community Center May-August 2002 (Box 5)
  - Annual Reports 1995-2001 (Box 5)
  - Back-ups (Box 5)
    (Back-ups are on a CD)
  - Bentley Historical Library June 2002 (Box 5)
  - Board of Directors
    - Banking Resolution (Box 5)
    - Binder
      - 1997-2001
        - Agendas (Box 5)
        - Finance and Hope Fund grant (Box 5)
        - Minutes, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - 2002
        - January (Box 5)
        - February (Box 5)
        - March (Box 5)
        - April (Box 5)
      - 2002-2003
        - Organizational chart, By-laws, contact information, and financial (Box 5)
        - Loose documents (Box 5)
        - January 2003-September 2003 (Box 5)
        - September 2002-December 2002 (Box 5)
        - May 2002-August 2002 (Box 5)
        - Reports (Box 5)
      - 2003, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Dynamics May 2006 (Box 5)
    - Finance report for meeting April 2002 (Box 5)
    - Letters of support, April -- May 2004 (Box 5)
    - Meeting agenda September 25, 2007 (Box 5)
      (Lease also in folder)
    - Meeting agendas and minutes
      - January 1999-November 1999 (Box 5)
      - October 2003-November 2003 (Box 5)
      - January 2004-January 2005 (Box 5)
      - August 2005-November 2005 (Box 5)
      - September 2005-December 2005 (Box 5)
        (Includes a board member's resignation)
      - January 2008-December 2008 (Box 5)
    - Nonprofit Enterprises at Work 2001 (Box 6)
    - Organizational chart and board member pledge August 2005 (Box 6)
    - Retreat
      - January 2001 (Box 6)
      - March 2002 (Box 6)
      - May 2006, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Volunteer Information Packet 2004 (Box 6)
  - Brochures 2002-2003 (Box 6)
  - By-laws undated (Box 6)
  - City Council meeting February 16, 1999 (Box 6)
  - Committees
    - Artists' coalition 2002 (Box 6)
    - Campaign chairperson committee (Box 6)
    - Development team December 2002-March 2003 (Box 6)
    - Executive committee
      - January -- February 2002 (Box 6)
      - August 2005 (Box 6)
    - Facilities committee August 2003 (Box 6)
    - Finance committee grant book 2001 (Box 6)
    - Fundraising 2002 (Box 6)
    - Fundraising development March-November 2003, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - L, G, B and Transgender Issues
      (formerly the American Friends Service Committee, Michigan Area Peace Education Committee)
      - Agendas and minutes 1993-2001 (Box 6)
      - Staff reports 1993-2001 (Box 6)
    - Membership
      - 2003 (Box 6)
      - 2004 (Box 6)
        (Membership donations and Washtenaw Pride registration)
    - Program committee
      - 2005 (Box 6)
      - 2006 (Box 6)
    - Public Policy
      - 2002 (Box 6)
      - 2002-2003 (Box 6)
      - 2003 (Box 6)
      - 2004 (Box 6)
      - 2005 (Box 6)
      - Corporate sponsorship policy drafting May 2005 (Box 7)
      - Discrimination-OZ nightclub 2005 (Box 7)
      - OZ nightclub 2005-2006 (Box 7)
      - Pentagon policy June 2006 (Box 7)
    - Strategic planning team -- nominations March 20, 2005 (Box 7)
    - Transgender Advocacy Project (TAP)
      - 2002-2003, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - 2002-2004 (Box 7)
      - 2004, 2 folders (Box 7)
      - 2006 (Box 7)
      - Blueprint to End Homelessness responses, June -- July 2004 (Box 7)
      - Housing and human rights concerns 1998, 2003 (Box 7)
      - Meetings and emails January-March 2003 (Box 7)
      - Trans Shelter Association February-August 2004 (Box 7)
    - Volunteer 2003 (Box 7)
  - Community meeting March 18, 2008 (Box 7)
    (Includes a meeting slideshow)
  - Coors Brewing Company corporate giving program 2006 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence 2003-2008 (Box 7)
  - Demographics
    - March 2001 (Box 7)
    - October 2002 (Box 7)
  - Development Audit and Gill Foundation community center imitative 2002-2004 (Box 7)
  - Donation thank-you letters, 2002(?) (Box 8)
  - Donations
    - Annual campaign
      - 2002 (Box 8)
      - 2003 (Box 8)
      - 2004 (Box 8)
    - December, 2000 (Box 8)
    - Holiday appeal
      - 2005 (Box 8)
      - 2007 (Box 8)
    - Membership Drive 2006 (Box 8)
    - Summer appeal 2007 (Box 8)
  - Drafts of The Big Book: WRAP Fundamentals, Policies and Procedures 2001, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - FERA
    - Evaluation report December 2001 (Box 8)
    - Needs Assessment plan September 2001 (Box 8)
  - Forms
    - Annual Membership undated (Box 8)
    - Community center and office use requests 2002-2004 (Box 8)
    - Community center group contact-completed, 2004(?) (Box 8)
    - Donations undated (Box 8)
    - Group contact -- completed, 2008(?) (Box 8)
    - Group contact, mailing list, message, and folder check undated (Box 8)
    - Group demographics -- completed
      - 2004 (Box 8)
      - 2005 (Box 8)
      - 2006 (Box 8)
      - 2007 (Box 8)
      - 2008 (Box 8)
    - Hate crimes report undated (Box 8)
    - HIV testing undated (Box 8)
    - Incoming call log -- completed January-November 2008 (Box 8)
    - Key holder agreement -- completed November 2004-May 2006 (Box 8)
    - Key requests -- completed circa 2003-2004 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous undated (Box 8)
    - Opening and closing procedure checklists -- completed March-April 2007 (Box 8)
    - Usage -- completed
      - 2005 (Box 8)
      - 2005-2006 (Box 8)
      - 2006 (Box 8)
      - 2007 (Box 8)
      - 2008 (Box 8)
    - Volunteer information, training checklist, and time log undated (Box 8)
    - Volunteer time logs --completed
      - December 2004-December 2006 (Box 8)
      - October 2006-- May 2008 (Box 8)
  - Group mailbox letter undated (Box 8)
  - History 2003-2004 (Box 8)
  - Lease 1998-2006 (Box 8)
  - Legal 1999-2003 (Box 8)
  - Mailing and contact lists 2006 (Box 8)
  - Mailing and membership lists 2002-2005 (Box 8)
  - Meeting notes
    - Community meeting 2007-2008 (Box 8)
    - Notebooks 2002, 2005 (Box 8)
    - Staff meeting
      - 2002 (Box 8)
      - 2003 (Box 8)
  - Membership
    - Business 1997-2001 (Box 8)
    - Correspondence 2002-2004 (Box 8)
    - Dues and contributions 1998-2000 (Box 8)
    - Incentives 2002-2003 (Box 8)
    - Referrals and processing flow chart 2003, 2007 (Box 8)
  - Membership issues and National Coming Out Day (NCOD) funds received 2002 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - 2002 (Box 9)
    - 2003-2006 (Box 9)
    - 2005-2006 (Box 9)
    - 2007 (Box 9)
  - Non-profit law
    - Alliance for Justice 2002 (Box 9)
    - Non-profit Corporation Act 2002 (Box 9)
  - Office -- layout, space usage, and maintenance 2001-2002 (Box 9)
  - Organizational chart 2002 (Box 9)
  - Policy
    - Consensual relationships with interns January-February 2004 (Box 9)
    - Discrimination and discriminatory harassment, addresses and phone numbers binder 2000-2003 (Box 9)
    - Grants April-May 2006 (Box 9)
    - Manuals, 2004(?) (Box 9)
      (Manuals are on 2 CDs)
    - Non-discrimination 1999 (Box 9)
  - Policy and procedures manual September 2001 (Box 9)
  - Public Relations archive 2004 (Box 9)
  - Public Relations statement for MCRI news conference at Triangle Foundation 2006 (Box 9)
  - President's book
    - 1999, 3 folders (Box 9)
    - 2000, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Raffle licenses
    - 1998-2000 (Box 9)
    - 2002-2004 (Box 9)
  - Resource list, 2005(?) (Box 9)
  - Resources
    - Business 2003 (Box 9)
    - Community 1998-2003 (Box 9)
    - Health undated (Box 9)
    - Non-profit 2003 (Box 9)
    - Spiritual 2004 (Box 9)
  - Staff
    - Directory (Box 9)
    - Executive director
      - Compensation (Box 9)
      - Job description and responsibilities (Box 9)
      - Klipp, Glenn (Box 9)
      - Search
        - Applications and interviews (Box 9)
        - Press release (Box 9)
    - Internship development (Box 9)
    - Katz, Beth (Box 9)
    - Office Manager
      - Job responsibilities (Box 9)
    - Volunteer coordination information (Box 9)
  - Solicitation licenses 2002-2005 (Box 9)
  - Volunteer book 2008 (Box 10)
  - Volunteer training packet 2004-2005 (Box 10)
  - Working Files
    - January 1999-December 2001 (Box 10)
    - February 1999-October 2001 (Box 10)
    - March 1999-September 2000 (Box 10)
    - January 2000-December 2000 (Box 10)
    - January 2001-April 2001 (Box 10)
    - February 2001-May 2001 (Box 10)
    - March 2001-September 2001, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - April 2001-November 2001 (Box 10)
    - December 2001 January 2003 (Box 10)
    - December 2001-June 2003 (Box 10)
    - January 2002-September 2005 (Box 10)
    - February 2002 (Box 11)
    - March 2002-December 2008, 2 folders (Box 11)
    - May 2002-October 2003 (Box 11)
      (Includes a Executive Director evaluation)
    - September 2002-May 2005 (Box 11)
    - October 2002-June 2003 (Box 11)
    - 2003-May 2007 (Box 11)
    - January 2003-April 2003 (Box 11)
    - February 2003-April 2003 (Box 11)
    - April 2003-May 2003 (Box 11)
    - April 2003-July 2003 (Box 11)
    - July 2003-September 2003 (Box 11)
    - October 2003-March 2004 (Box 11)
    - December 2003-March 2004 (Box 11)
      (Includes documents from a 2007 retreat)
    - December 2003-July 2004 (Box 11)
    - March 2004-July 2005 (Box 11)
    - June 2004-April 2005 (Box 12)
    - July 2004-February 2005 (Box 12)
    - August 2004-December 2004 (Box 12)
    - September 2004-July 2006 (Box 12)
    - October 2004-February 2005 (Box 12)
    - January 2005-September 2005 (Box 12)
      (Contains a very small number of documents from August 2007)
    - February 2005-April 2005 (Box 12)
    - March 2005-January 2006 (Box 12)
    - April 2005-January 2006, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - May 2005-September 2005 (Box 12)
    - January 2006-February 2007 (Box 12)
      (Includes a development audit from March 2003)
    - January 2006-March 2007 (Box 12)
    - January 2006-May 2009, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - August 2006-December 2007 (Box 12)
    - January 2007-February 2007 (Box 12)
    - February 2007-October 2007 (Box 13)
    - June 2007-January 2008 (Box 13)
    - September 2007-November 2007 (Box 13)
    - September 2007-December 2007 (Box 13)
    - June 2009-March 2010 (Box 13)
    - March 2010-September 2011 (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous, 2001-2007(?) (Box 13)
- Education and Outreach
  The Education and Outreach series focuses on WRAP's efforts to improve the lives of the LGBT community by supporting activities such as an anti-violence campaign and an HIV/AIDS awareness program within Washtenaw County. WRAP also invested a great deal of time in promoting tolerance and awareness within public schools as a local chapter of the Gay, Lesbian, Straight Education Network.
  - Ann Arbor Pride Picnic 1999 (Box 2)
  - Anti-Violence Project -- Correspondence and Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 2)
  - City of Ann Arbor HIV/AIDS Task Force 1992-1994, 6 folders (Box 2)
  - Equality Begins at Home 1996 (Box 2)
  - Educational programs 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Gay, Lesbian, Straight Education Network (GLSEN)
    - Accreditation 1998-2000 (Box 2)
    - Agendas 1997-2000 (Box 2)
    - Board Meetings 1998-1999 (Box 2)
    - Board Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence 1998-1999 (Box 2)
    - Correspondence 2000 (Box 2)
    - Forsythe Middle School -- Discrimination (Box 2)
    - Midwest Conference 1998 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous administration (Box 2)
    - Minutes and membership 1998-1999 (Box 3)
    - Outreach materials (Box 3)
    - Publications 2000 (Box 3)
  - Hate crimes media coverage 1997 (Box 3)
  - LGB youth center
    - 1995 (Box 3)
    - 1996 (Box 3)
    - 1997 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 3)
  - Other organizations -- flyers (Box 3)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force -- Position papers 1995 (Box 3)
  - Queer Youth (Box 3)
  - Queer Youth -- Youth Needs Survey (Box 3)
  - Referral Lists (Box 3)
  - Rainbow Oasis Center
    - Administrative (Box 3)
    - Agendas (Box 3)
    - Board Meeting Minutes 1995-1996 (Box 3)
    - Bylaws (Box 3)
    - Correspondence 1995-1997 (Box 3)
    - Correspondence undated (Box 3)
    - Executive Committee Minutes 1995 (Box 3)
    - Funding Committee 1995 (Box 3)
    - General Announcements (Box 3)
    - General Meeting Minutes 1995-1996 (Box 3)
    - Other Publications (Box 3)
    - Other activities 1994-1997 (Box 3)
  - Special Events 1995-1999 (Box 3)
  - Volunteer opportunities 1999 (Box 3)
  - Youth/Adult partnership summit 1999 (Box 3)
- Political Action
  The Political Action series documents WRAP's continuing interest in maintaining a high political profile within the community. Plans for the annual National Coming Out Day celebration, the Millennium March on Washington, and other activities are contained in this series.
  - Ann Arbor Art Fair 1996 (Box 3)
  - Capitol Commitment 1996-1997 (Box 3)
  - Gender Identity 1999 (Box 3)
  - Lansing Pride 1999 (Box 3)
  - Hate Crimes/AVP/Triangle 1995 (Box 3)
  - Information on Other States' Anti-Gay Ballot Measures 1994 (Box 3)
  - "Love Makes a Family" Exhibit May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Barney Frank -- Correspondence 1997 (Box 3)
  - Meeting with Barney Frank -- Preparatory Materials 1997 (Box 3)
  - Michigan Pride March, 1996 (Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous Events 1997 (Box 3)
  - Millennium March on Washington -- Meeting February 1996 (Box 3)
  - Millennium March on Washington -- Organizational Information 1999-2000, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - National Coming Out Day
    - 1995 (Box 3)
    - 1996 (Box 3)
    - 1997
      - Correspondence (Box 3)
      - Publicity (Box 3)
    - 1998
      - Armistead Maupin (Box 3)
      - Budget and Planning (Box 3)
      - Budget and Tickets (Box 3)
      - Correspondence (Box 4)
      - Dinner/Cocktail Party (Box 4)
      - General Information (Box 4)
      - Press/Media (Box 4)
      - Sponsorship Information (Box 4)
      - Ticket Sales (Box 4)
    - 1999 (Box 4)
  - Other Organizations
    - GAMBOC (Gay and Bisexual Men of Color) (Box 4)
    - LGBA 1994-1996 (Box 4)
    - Press Releases 1996-2000 (Box 4)
  - Political Summit
    - 1995 (Box 4)
    - 1996 (Box 4)
  - Pride June 1995 (Box 4)
  - Spring Summit 1997 (Box 4)
  - Various LGBT Events (Box 4)
  - Ypsilanti, MI Anti-Discrimination Ordinance 1995-1997 (Box 4)
  - Ypsilanti, MI CFE Ordinance 1998 (Box 4)
- Events
  The Events series (1.5 linear feet) documents the planning, arranging, and involvement by WRAP staff in creating events for the benefit of, and to engage, the Washtenaw County community. Events of note include OutFest, a partnered dinner and silent auction with the Human Rights Campaign, and smaller events such as Pride Picnic and a Commitment Ceremony for same-sex couples.
  - Art Fair
    - 2001-2002 (Box 13)
    - 2003 (Box 13)
    - 2005 (Box 13)
  - Art fundraiser April 27, 2002 (Box 13)
  - Commitment Ceremony
    - Certificate application 2004 (Box 13)
    - Ceremony and Holy Union June 14, 2003 (Box 13)
    - Planning April 2003 (Box 13)
  - Diversity Dinner
    - Governor Granholm -- keynote speaker invitation September 2013 (Box 13)
    - Planning May-July 2013 (Box 13)
  - Evening of Recognition and Remembrance
    - 2004-2005 (Box 13)
    - 2006, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Film Festival
    - 2003, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - 2005 (Box 13)
  - Human Rights Campaign (HRC) Dinner
    - 1999 (Box 13)
    - 2001-2002 (Box 13)
    - 2002 (Box 13)
    - Auction
      - Undated (Box 13)
      - 2001, 2 folders (Box 13)
      - 2002 (Box 14)
    - Auction guide and volunteer solicitation 2001 (Box 14)